Guide to the Center for American Music Photos CAM.PHOTOS.2017
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Henrietta Crosman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 646)
  - Henrietta Crosman in costume holding a rapier (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.03)
  - Henrietta Crosman in costume holding a flower (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.04)
  - Henrietta Crosman dressed as a man seated across from another man in costume (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.05)
  - Henrietta Crosman and a man dueling in The Sword of the King (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.06)
  - Henrietta Crosman and other actors posing in The Sword of the King (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.07)
  - Henrietta Crosman in costume having her hand kissed by a man in costume (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.08)
  - Henrietta Crossman wearing a dress and pearl broach (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.09)
  - Henrietta Crosman wearing a gown and pearl necklaces seated in a chair (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.1)
  - Henrietta Crosman dressed as a man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.11)
  - Henrietta Crosman posing on set with other actors in Mistress Nell (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.12)
  - Henrietta Crosman dressed as a man seated in a chair (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.13)
  - Henrietta Crosman and another actor in the balcony scene from Mistress Nell (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.14)
  - Henrietta Crosman in costume for Mistress Nell and Nance Oldfield (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.15)
  - Profile portrait of Henrietta Crosman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 646.16)
- Morrison Foster, 1890 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 647)
- Morrison Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 648)
- Morrison Foster seated at a desk, 1887 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 649)
- Morrison Foster, Rebecca S. Foster, Rosy Gescha, William B. Foster (infant) and Evelyn Olver Foster, 1890 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 650)
- Evelyn Louise Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 651)
  - Evelyn Louise Foster as an infant (tintype) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 651.01)
  - Evelyn Louise Foster and Amy Collins (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 651.02)
  - Evelyn Louise Foster, April 1879 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 651.03)
  - Evelyn Louise Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 651.04)
- Evelyn Louise Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 652)
- Evelyn Louise Foster and an unidentified man, July 5, 1880 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 653)
- Evelyn Louise Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 654)
- Richard Knowlson Foster as a toddler seated in a rocking chair (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 655)
- "Mother", 1890 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 656)
- Jessie Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 657)
  - Jessie Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 657.01)
  - Jessie Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 657.02)
- Items from Foster Hall Collection, March 5, 1996 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 658)
  - Items from Foster Hall Collection: The Five Nice Young Men (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 658.01)
  - Items from Foster Hall Collection: New Orleans Serenaders poster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 658.02)
  - Items from Foster Hall Collection: The Streets of Philadelphia poster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 658.03)
  - Items from Foster Hall Collection: Poster for the New Orleans Serenaders at the Boston Museum, July 15th (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 658.04)
- Cover of Stephen Foster book in Japanese (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 659)
- Photos from the Nevin Collection
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: oval portrait of Anne Paul Nevin (Folder 18, Drawer 1, Photos 660)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin in Dresden, age 15, 1878 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.01)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin age 6 years old, 1869 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.02)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin at the age of fourteen, 1877 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.03)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin age five years old, 1868 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.04)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Jane Cree Oliphant, Nevin's maternal grandmother (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.05)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin aged four years old, 1867 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.06)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin's nurse "Viney" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.07)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin with his Nurse (Viney) age 1 year, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.08)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin aged 2 years old, 1865 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.09)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Oliphant, the Uncle for whom Ethelbert Nevin was named (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.1)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Elizabeth Oliphant Nevin, Ethelbert Nevin's Mother, and Lily Nevin, Ethelbert's younger sister (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.11)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin age fifteen years old, 1878 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.12)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Mrs. Gustav Schirmer (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.13)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: drawing of Sarah Nevin Henderson (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.14)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Elizabeth Duncan Oliphant Nevin, Ethelbert Nevin's mother (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.15)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Home of Ethelbert Nevin in Venice, 1896 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.16)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Vineacre exterior in Sewickley, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.17)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Entrance to Vineacre, Nevin's home in Sewickley, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.18)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Entrance to Vineacre, birthplace of Ethelbert Nevin in Sewickley, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.19)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin with his older brother Hughes Nevin, 1871 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 661.2)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin at Vineacre, 1898 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 662.02)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin with children in Sewickley (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 662.03)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: House in which Ethelbert Nevin died on February 17, 1901 in New Haven, CT (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 662.04)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin in New York, 1898 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 662.05)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Doris Nevin (daughter of Ethelbert Nevin) dressed as Little Bo Peep in New Haven, CT (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 662.06)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin with his "Little Choir" at Vineacre in Sewickley, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 662.07)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Robert P. Nevin (Ethelbert Nevin's Father) on the porch at Vineacre in Sewickley, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 662.08)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: House -- Queen Anne's Lodge (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 662.09)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: House where EWN and APN lived, 1888-1889, in Quincy, Mass (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 662.11)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin at His Piano (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 663)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Unknown woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 664)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Father Nevin in the Library at Vineacre (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 665)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Thomas Dickson of Sewickley, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 666.01)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Clara Dickson (Mrs. Thomas Dickson), Ethelbert Nevin's Sunday School Teacher at the Sewickley Presbyterian Church (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 666.02)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Lizzie Dickson of Sewickley, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 666.03)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Clara Dickson, boyhood friend of Ethelbert Nevin (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 666.04)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: View from the terrace at Arcady (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 666.05)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin silhouette (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 666.06)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Parlor at Vineacre (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 666.07)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Nevin Family in parlor at Vineacre (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 666.08)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin, 1886 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 667)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Studio photograph of Ronald Coleman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 668)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin in her wedding dress, 1888 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 670.01)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin in Pittsburgh while a student at Bishop Bowman's Institute, 1880 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 670.02)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin in London (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 670.03)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin in her bedroom playing the banjo at Edgewater, 1881 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 670.04)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin in Pittsburgh, 1883 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 670.05)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin as a student in Berlin, 1885 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 670.06)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin and Anne Paul Nevin (not in Nevin Finding Aid) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 670.07)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul's bedroom at Edgewater, Oakmont (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 670.08)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin's Bedroom in Edgewater, Oakmont, 1881 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 670.09)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Music room of Ethelbert Nevin on Park St. in Boston, 1887-1888 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 670.1)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: St. Peter's Episcopal Church, Grant Street, where Ethelbert and Anne Paul Nevin were married, 1888 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 670.11)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Music room, New Haven, 1901 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 671)
  - Photos from the Nevin collection: "Our First House" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 672)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Elizabeth C. Adams, November 8, 1888 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 675.01)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin with son Paul Nevin, 1889 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 675.02)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Adams House (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 675.03)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Music Room at Ouasi, Florida (Father Paul's residence), 1893 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 675.04)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Tennis tournament, September 3, 1888 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 675.05)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin; on reverse of photo is a partial postcard written in ink by Willa Cather (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 676)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin with daughter Doris looking at each other (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 677.01)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin with daughter Doris (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 677.02)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 677.03)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin wearing a large feathered hat (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 677.04)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin standing, wearing a knotted string of pearls (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 677.05)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin standing, wearing a white dress (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 677.06)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin close up wearing a hat (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 677.07)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin seated wearing a velvet coat and hat (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 677.08)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Nevin collection exhibit at Musical Americana in State Museum (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 678.01)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Nevin collection exhibit at Musical Americana in State Museum (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 678.02)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Margaret Williams Nevin, Ethelbert Nevin's paternal grandmother (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 679)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Signed photograph of Karl Klindworth, 1887 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 680)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin, Richard Harding Davis and C. B. Davis, 1896 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 681)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Sibyl Sanderson, May 26, 1896 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 682)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Marie Bremer, May 26, 1896 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 683)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Daniel Gregory Mason, a student of Ethelbert Nevin's (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 684)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin with Charles Scovel, July 1884 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 685.01)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin when a student in Berlin (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 685.02)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin with Elbert Baldwin, 1885 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 685.03)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Mother and Father Nevin, Ethelbert Nevin, Anne Paul Nevin, Nell Paul, and Elbert Baldwin on the way to Beyreuth, 1885 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 685.04)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin with Elizabeth "Lizzie" Dickson (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 685.05)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin with Charles Scovel in Berlin, 1885 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 685.06)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin with Mr. and Mrs. Jacob W, Anne Paul, and Elbert Baldwin, 1885 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 685.07)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin with C.V. Thompson, Isaac Craig, and C. W. Scovel, September 15, 1884 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 685.08)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin aged 19 in Boston, 1883 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 685.09)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin wearing the stickpin Anne Paul gave him when they became engaged, 1884 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 685.1)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Richard Harding Davis, 1891 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 687.01)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin and children (Paul and Doris) in Florence, 1895 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 687.02)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin's Grave at Arcady, from foot (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 688.01)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Close up of Nevin's gravestone at Arcady (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 688.02)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin's grave at Arcady, from side (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 688.03)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Elizabeth "Lizzie" Dickson of Sewickley seated at Ethelbert Nevin's piano in the Cathedral of Learning, 1938 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 689)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin at his desk at Queen Anne's Lodge, Vineacre, Sewickley, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 690)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Ethelbert Nevin with Elbert Baldwin, 1885 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 691)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Clothilde von Finck at whose home Nevin lived while a student in Germany (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 692.01)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Clothilde von Finck in Berlin, July 1886 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 692.02)
  - Photos from the Nevin Collection: Anne Paul Nevin (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 694)
- "Old Folks at Home Variations" manuscript (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 698)
  - Pages 1 and 2 of "Old Folks at Home Variations" manuscript (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 698.01)
  - Pages 3 and 4 of "Old Folks at Home Variations" manuscript (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 698.02)
  - Page 4 close up of "Old Folks at Home Variations" manuscript (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 698.03)
- "Hard Times Come Along No More" broadside (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 699)
- Laying the Cornerstone for the Stephen Foster Memorial, 1937 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 700)
- Bill Shustik (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 701)
- Stephen Foster The Musical Cast (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 702)
- Pitt Men's Glee Club trip to White Springs, FL, May 1996 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 703)
  - Pitt Men's Glee Club trip to White Springs, FL: Pitt Men's Glee Club standing in front of the White Springs Museum (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 703.01)
  - Pitt Men's Glee Club trip to White Springs, FL: Sign for the entrance to the Stephen Foster State Folk Culture Center (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 703.02)
  - Pitt Men's Glee Club trip to White Springs, FL: Carillion at the Stephen Foster State Folk Culture Center (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 703.03)
- Josiah Kirby Lilly with his grandchildren (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 704)
  - Josiah Kirby Lilly with his three grandchildren (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 704.01)
  - Josiah Kirby Lilly with his grandson on his lap (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 704.02)
- Head shot of Joe Negri holding his guitar (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 705)
- Frederic Holder's oil portrait of Stephen Collins Foster, January 1963 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 706)
- Billy and Ethel, March 1920 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 707)
- Richard Foster as an infant, March 1927 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 708)
  - Dick Foster, aged 6 months (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 708.01)
  - Dick Foster aged six months (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 708.02)
  - Dick Foster (?) sitting on the exterior steps of a house (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 708.03)
- Charles Z. Klauder architectural drawing of the exterior of the Foster Memorial (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 709)
- Harry T. Burleigh (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 710)
- Christy's New Songster and Blackjack, 1863 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 711)
- Cover for I.W.W. Songs songster (M1664.L3 I6 1936) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 712)
- Cover for Dvorak in America by Joseph Horowitz (ML3930.D9 H67 2003) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 713)
- Engraving of Augusta College (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 714)
- Letter from Henrietta Foster to Morrison Foster, June 21, 1853 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 715)
  - Letter from Henrietta Foster to Morrison Foster, page 1 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 715.01)
  - Letter from Henrietta Foster to Morrison Foster, Page 2 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 715.02)
  - Letter from Henrietta Foster to Morrison Foster, page 3 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 715.03)
- Sheet music cover for "Nelly was a Lady" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 716)
- Sheet of Ethelbert Nevin 10 cent postage stamps (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 717)
- Sheet music cover for Ethelbert Nevin's "Narcissus" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 718)
- Bellevue Hospital, NY, plot plan (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 740)
- Painting of E.P. Christy (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 743)
  - Painting of E.P. Christy (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 743.01)
  - Rear of canvas of painting of E.P. Christy (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 743.02)
- Man holding an oar standing next to a wheelbarrow full of dead birds (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 744)
- Plan for Stephen Foster houses in New York (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 745)
- Stephen Foster School in Bellflower, California (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 746)
- Suwanee River (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 747)
- Wildflower exhibit (?) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 753)
- Display on Foster at Farmer's National Bank, 1937 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 754)
- Portrait of an unidentified woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 755)
- portrait of unidentified man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 756)
- Painting of Stephen Foster by Howard Chandler Christy (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 757)
- Unidentified woman wearing a large satin hat (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 758)
- Negative image of etching of "Pittsburg, Pennsylvania" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 759)
- Negative image of Nelson Kneass (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 760)
- Sheet music for Foster's "Oh Susanna" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 761)
  - Cover for "Oh Susanna" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 761.01)
  - Page 3 of Foster's "Oh Susanna" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 761.02)
  - Page 4 of Foster's "Oh Susanna" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 761.03)
  - page 5 of Foster's "Oh Susanna" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 761.04)
- An identified dog (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 762)
- Unidentified man standing under palm trees with a hat at his feet (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 763)
- Pearl Caldwell (Campbell), 1905 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 764)
- Cincinnati, Ohio, waterfront, 1848 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 765)
  - "Cincinnati" by Fontayne and Porter, 1848 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 765.01)
  - Cincinnati waterfront showing office of Irwin and Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 765.02)
  - Cincinnati waterfront showing the packet "Brooklyn" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 765.03)
  - Cincinnati waterfront (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 765.04)
  - Cincinnati Waterfront showing the "Ohio Belle" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 765.05)
  - Cincinnati waterfront (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 765.06)
  - Cincinnati Waterfront (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 765.07)
  - Cincinnati waterfront (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 765.08)
- Scrapbook page showing three photos of the Stephen Foster Memorial Home at 3600 Penn Avenue, with typed captions (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 766)
- Olver Place (Morrison Foster's home) in Sewickley (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 767)
  - Morrison and Rebecca Foster standing on the porch of Olver Place, 1903 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 767.01)
  - Front of Olver Place (Morrison Foster's home), Sewickley, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 767.02)
  - Front of Olver Place (Morrison Foster's home), Sewickley, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 767.03)
- Ann Crosman Fawcett (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 768)
- Henrietta Crosman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 770)
  - Henrietta Crosman in Mistress Nell (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 770.01)
  - Henrietta Crosman in costume as a man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 770.02)
  - Henrietta Crosman in a floor length brocade gown holding flowers (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 770.03)
  - Henrietta Crosman in costume as a man kneeling on a chair (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 770.04)
  - Henrietta Crosman wearing a gown and a large hat (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 770.05)
  - Henrietta Crosman in costume as a man holding a rapier (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 770.06)